CURRICULUM VITAE

MUSA-AZEEZ, Taslim Eniola

taslim.eniolla@gmail.com 0708-471-2978 https://github.com/TASLIM-ENIOLLA

A. PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a friendly and proficient full stack web developer with zeal for developing problem solving-system with several year of experience in learning modern web development skill and development stacks. I am an excellent team player with interpersonal skill. I have collaborations with other developer both home and abroad. I have developed a number of web sites and web applications that render a service or solves a problem.

Notable among these projects is TranXfer Cloud: A online based file storage where users can store files and retrieve them on a latter date. Come next is an Online Medical Diagnostics System: An online portal where patients can interact with a Bot which queries for symptoms and can predict with a high level of accuracy if the patient is infected with Covid 19 or not. Another is a surveillance system using Python's OpenCV framework. These projects earned me my expertise and proficiency which gives me an edge over a large number of developers out there.

B. PERSONAL DATA

Name Musa-Azeez, Taslim Eniola

Date of Birth 19th of April, 2001

Nationality Nigerian

State of Origin Oyo

Permanent Home Address Block J, Plot 11, LSDPC Estate, Gonwun, Ogijo, Shagamu LGA, Ogun

State.

Present Position Undergraduate

Contact Details Email <u>taslim.eniolla@gmail.com</u>

Phone <u>0708-471-2978</u>

Github https://github.com/TASLIM-ENIOLLA

Repository



C. EDUCATION

2017 Till Date

B.Sc. in Information & Communication Science (Faculty of Communication & Information Sciences), University

of Ilorin, Nigeria. P.O.Box 1515. Maintained a Second Class Upper GPA Till Date.

2016 General Certificate Examination, Government Girls Secondary School, FESTAC, Lagos State, Nigeria. (2

Distinctions, 6 Credits, 1 pass).

2014 - 2016 Senior Secondary School, Great Esteem Secondary School, Sanya Junction, Apapa-Oshodi Express Way, Lagos.

2011 - 2014 Junior Secondary School, Iman College, Mopol Junction, Off Ago-Okota Road, Amuwo-Odofin, Mile 2, Lagos.

2006 - 2011 Primary Leaving Certificate, Amuwo-Odofin Muslim Community Private School (AOMCPS). Maintained Top 3

Position from Primary One to Five

D. INTERNSHIP

Mar. - Sept., 2020 SOFTRAYS INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

I had my internship program at the above mentioned organization where I got to acquire some skills and got certifications for them. The skill I acquired are listed below:

• Graphics Design

• Full Stack Web Developement

AutoCAD 3D Designs

• Network Administration

• Digital Marketing

E. WORK EXPERIENCE

Organization Accomplishments

2022 Till Date CodeHub Technological Institute Worked closely with software development members to

 $\ design \ and \ meet \ client's \ requirements \ for \ functionality,$

scalibility and performance.

2022 Till Date Sulham Technical Services Worked as a fullstack developer to develop systems that

provide solution to existing problems.

Sept Nov., 2020	Softrays Information Technology		Worked as an instructor having tutored six students who have now become proficient in frontend web development Worked as Registration Area Technical (RATECH) Officer During General Elections in Osi LGA, Kwara State with my team of Youth Corps in ensuring election results are accounted for and uploaded to the central server.	
Mar Apr., 2019	INEC Nigeria	During General El team of Youth Co		
F. SKILL SET (HARD SKILLS)				
Skill	Proficiency	Skill	Proficiency	
HTML & CSS	90%	MySQL	83%	
React Js	93%	MongoDB	70%	
Next Js	95%	AutoCAD	80%	
РНР	85%	Network Administration	85%	
Python	72%	Cisco Packet Tracer	79%	
Express Js	78%	MS Office	75%	
G. SKILL SET (SOFT SKILLS)				
Skill		Proficiency		
Interpersonal Relationship		80%		
Team leadership		70%		
Punctuality		80%		
H. LANGUAGES				
language		Proficiency		
English		90%		
Yoruba 9		90%		
I. CERTIFICATIONS				
Fullstack Web Developement	CCNA - Cisco Certified Network Associate	AutoCAD 3D Designs Grap	hics Design Digital Marketing	
J. INTERESTS	CCNA - Cisco Certified Network Associate	AutoCAD 3D Designs Grap	hics Design Digital Marketing	

Worked as a developer for over ten clients, converting

their software needs into working software solutions. \\

Fiverr Freelancer

K. PORTFOLIO

2020 Till Date

Visit http://taslim-eniolla.vercel.app to view portfolio.